Thank you for watching!
I was very nervous today,
I was very nervous today, but I had a good time talking with Yakan-kun,
I think I was able to shorten the distance between me and Yakan-kun a little,
It was a very enjoyable recording.
I feel that Gumi can talk forever.
In the past, we used to have a lot of Earth Gummi, but this year we have Narslope Gummi,
This year, I think we will be including these long and thin Korean gummy bears called "Narslope Gummi.
I am paying attention to them.
Surprisingly, I also like simple and plain gummy bears.
My favorite gummy bears are simple and have nothing in them.
But sometimes, when I want something stimulating, I eat sour gummy bears with a coating around them.
Please look forward to the next installment!
I think someone said "cute.
I think Sorami said it, didn't she?
It's for gummy bears.
That way?
The one whispering "cute" to me?
But I want to produce Gummi myself.
I'd like to be on posters or something.
It's hard to tell what you've lost by talking too fast.
It's hard to hear, and it's hard to communicate, so it's pretty hard to get the message across.
The good thing about speaking fast is that I can say what I want to say even if the time is short.
It's my time to talk fast.
It's my lurie time.
I said I love the camera, but I'm not very good with it.
I close my eyes, you know?
It's a one-sided love.
To the camera.
It has curls.
Cute.
I asked her what she does on her day off,
I'm wondering what you do on your day off,
I would like to ask her what she does on her day off.
I know that she likes to play games a lot,
I think she probably plays games.
What do you think?
Cute!
So, what do you have in mind?
I think that among the staff-run, I'd like to talk to
I would like to talk to Hitoko Takai of the Super-Tokiimeki Advertising Department.
I'd like to know how she builds her body.
She has a very good style.
I'd like to hear about how she maintains her body.
See you soon!
I'm hungry.
Oh, there are gummy bears!
Crunch! Like that.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Thank you for watching!
Has the song been released yet?
Yes, we have.
This is our debut song.
It's not the original song.
It's a song that I've been working on since I joined the band.
I'm still not used to having my voice on the soundtrack.
It's been a year.
I see... I see... I see...
Sometimes my voice doesn't sound like my voice.
I haven't
You should record it.
What? We used to walk down Takeshita-dori together.
My dad met him a lot.
I see.
It's like he knows me better than I know myself.
He knows me better than I know myself.
You got me again.
Well, he was my parent. I guess male parents do that.
Really?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, do you have any siblings?
I have an older brother.
You have a brother?
How's your brother? What's your brother's reaction?
He came to our first show.
He hasn't come to any shows since then.
I've invited him a few times.
He's a bit of a tsundere, but he hasn't come.
Oh man, he's so shy.
He's a little embarrassed.
How big are you?
Four years older.
Four years older?
Four?
I'm so proud of you, aren't I?
No, no, no, no, no.
Just like that.
He's looking forward to his major label debut.
I'm looking forward to it.
I see.
Are there going to be storytelling sessions?
We do storytelling sessions.
Aren't you good at storytelling?
I'm very good at them.
But I think the fans probably have a little bit of trouble hearing me because I'm too fast.
It's a little bit hard for them to understand me.
I'd like to do social distance at this time of the year.
Do you have storytelling sessions during these times?
I think it's going to be a storytelling session while we're filming.
So, what? What? You'll be like, "What?
Yes! I'm sure it will be!
I'm so excited about that story, too.
What? It's like...
Oh, really?
Yes, it is.
It's fun. It's funny.
It's nice.
I like it.
Yes, I do.
Have you ever been happy to hear
What made you happy?
I was told that I've become a fan of Ruri.
I wasn't sure who I should nominate, but now I'm really happy to hear that she's my nominee.
But I was really happy to be told that I'm going to guess Ruri.
Are you happy?
That you chose me out of 6 people.
That made me really happy.
That's right.
If I were Akane's fan...
But Uni-chan is a fan who pushes harder...
That's hard to answer, isn't it, senpai?
Do you do it with a big smile? I don't know...
It's not easy to do that around here, is it?
It makes me very happy when he pushes harder.
More push?
It's nice to get a little extra.
It's sad.
I know, right? Do you get more pushback?
I'm a little sad when someone pushes more besides me.
But if I'm on the receiving end, I'd be very happy.
Really?
First of all, please increase.
I understand.
It makes me a little sad.
Like, "Oh, you increased it.
I see.
Yes, it does.